[Applause]
[Music]
part
two number seven how would you like me
to prepare your
coffee a she's making copies B from the
local Cafe C black with no
sugar number eight when will I be
informed about the status of my
application a a promotion within 2
months B sometime around Thursday C you
can do that on our
website number nine do you know where
the office supplies happen to be a we
buy from alpha
stationary B it came as a total
surprise C look in the storage
closet number 10 shall I save a seat for
you in the
cafeteria a yeah the new Cafe has great
seats B that's fine I'm already sitting
here see no I'm going to eat at my
desk number 11 shouldn't you be heading
to the conference room in a few minutes
a no the meeting got
cancelled B sure I'll call you in half
an hour C yes we're ahead of our
competitors number 12 is it possible to
have cable TV installed at my home a
there's a game on channel 10 B if you
pay an installation fee c a house at 54
Rosemont
Avenue number
13 why did Mr Martinson request Miss
Johnson's work file a she works in the
marketing
department B to review her performance
last year C you'll have to file your own
request number 14 is it your turn to
drive tomorrow or is it mine a neither
Jane's driving B I'll drive you home
today C I'm pretty sure that's
right number 15 we had better order some
more food for the event a two large
pizzas and a picture of soda B it's
going to take place on Friday night C
you're right more people are attending
it number
16 why hasn't the appliance that I
ordered been mailed yet a you can get a
discount on it B I ordered it last
Monday C it's not in stock at the
warehouse number
17 you're picking the German deleg up at
the airport aren't you a they'll be here
for the next 2 weeks B Jeremy
volunteered to go there instead see she
delegated several tasks to
me number 18 who's giving the
presentation at the staff
meeting a it's going to start at 8:00
sharp B we can open the presents later
in the day C Ken told me that Miss Ruiz
is doing
that number
19 how quickly can we get the fax
machine
repaired a it was around several years
ago B let's call the service provider
and ask C sure I'll send you my fax
number number 20 what do you you think
about purchasing tickets for next
Wednesday's
concert a go ahead and buy a couple for
me please B it's going to feature some
popular bands C everyone on the team
should act in
concert number
21 why haven't the survey results been
published a it hit the best seller list
after being published B all the data is
still being compiled C sure I don't mind
taking a
survey number
22 could you please direct me to the
marketing
department a take a right at the third
intersection B follow me I'm going there
now C he's quite an experienced
marketer number
23 someone had better assist that
customer who has been
waiting a I'm free so I'll give her a
hand B it's our job to provide customer
assistance C I've been waiting for
almost an
hour number
24 when is the commercial for the new
product line going to air a sometime
during the middle of the week B B it
features all kinds of new
Cosmetics c yeah she's done something
new with her
hair number
25 what about purchasing a laptop
instead of a
desktop a this one is too costly B they
bought it last week C I'd prefer not to
do that
number
26 how much money do I owe you for these
items a don't worry it's my treat B I
deposited it in your account C there are
five of them in
total number
27 what caused the power to go out all
over the
city a I don't know why my phone has no
power B some electric lines got knocked
down C there will be thunderstorms next
week number 28 don't forget to submit
your nominations for the employee of the
month a thanks I can't believe that I
won B yes he was nominated again C I
turned mine in to Claris already
number
29 when can you send someone to look at
the air conditioner a it's not very cool
in this room B I can't find anything
wrong with it C A repairman will be
there by
two number 30 I wonder what's taking Mr
Yeet so long a he called and said he's
caught in traffic B this is much longer
than I had expected C he's looking
forward to meeting
everyone number
31 which type of wallpaper would look
best in this room a I've never put up
wallpaper before B this is going to be
my office C they all seem all right to
me
[Music]
number seven how would you like me to
prepare your
coffee a she's making copies B from the
local Cafe C black with no sugar
number eight when will I be informed
about the status of my
application a a promotion within 2
months B sometime around Thursday C you
can do that on our
website number nine do you know where
the office supplies happen to be a we
buy from alpha
stationary B it came as a total surprise
C look in the storage
closet number 10 shall I save a seat for
you in the
cafeteria a yeah then new Cafe has great
seats B that's fine I'm already sitting
here C no I'm going to eat at my
desk number 11
shouldn't you be heading to the
conference room in a few
minutes a no the meeting got
cancelled B sure I'll call you in half
an hour C yes we're ahead of our
competitors number 12 is it possible to
have cable TV installed at my home a
there's a game on channel 10 B if you
pay an installation fee c a house at 54
Rosemont
Avenue number
13 why did Mr Martinson request Miss
Johnson's work file a she works in the
marketing
department B to review her performance
last year C you'll have to file your own
request
number
14 is it your turn to drive tomorrow or
is it mine a neither Jane's driving B
I'll drive you home today C I'm pretty
sure that's
right number 15 we had better order some
more food for the event a two large
pizzas and a pitch of soda B it's going
to take place on Friday night see you're
right more people are attending
it number
16 why hasn't the appliance that I
ordered been mailed yet a you can get a
discount on it B I ordered it last
Monday C it's not in stock at the
warehouse number
17 you're picking the German delegation
up at the airport aren't you a they'll
be here for the next two weeks B Jeremy
volunteered to go there instead C she
delegated several tasks to
me number 18 who's giving the
presentation at the staff
meeting a it's going to start at 8:00
sharp B we can open the presents later
in the day C Ken told me that Miss Ruiz
is doing
that number
19 how quickly can we get the fax
machine
repaired a it was around several years
ago B let's call the service provider
and ask C sure I'll send you my fax
number
number 20 what do you think about
purchasing tickets for next Wednesday's
concert a go ahead and buy a couple for
me please B it's going to feature some
popular bands C everyone on the team
should act in
concert number
21 why haven't the survey results been
published a it hit the best seller list
after being published B all the data is
still being compiled C sure I don't mind
taking a
survey number
22 could you please direct me to the
marketing
department a take a right at the third
intersection B follow me I'm going there
now C he's quite an experienced marketer
number
23 someone had better assist that
customer who has been
waiting a I'm free so I'll give her a
hand B it's our job to provide customer
assistance C I've been waiting for
almost an
hour number
24 when is the commercial for the new
product line going to air a sometime
during the middle of the week B it
features all kinds of new
Cosmetics c yeah she's done something
new with her
hair number
25 what about purchasing a laptop
instead of a
desktop a this one is too costly B they
bought it last week C I'd prefer not to
do that
number
26 how much money do I owe you for these
items a don't worry it's my treat B I
deposited it in your account C there are
five of them in
total number
27 what caused the power to go out all
over the
city a I don't know why my phone has no
power B some electric lines got knocked
down C there will be thunderstorms next
week number 28 don't forget to submit
your nominations for the employee of the
month a thanks I can't believe that I
won B yes he was nominated again C I
turned mine in to Claris already
number
29 when can you send someone to look at
the air conditioner a it's not very cool
in this room B I can't find anything
wrong with it C A repairman will be
there by
to number 30 I wonder what's taking Mr
Yeet so long a he called and said he's
caught in traffic B this is much longer
than I had expected C he's looking
forward to meeting
everyone number
31 which type of wallpaper would look
best in this room a I've never put up
wallpaper before B this is going to be
my office C they all seem all right to
me
e e